夕阳消失在地平线
万家灯火逐渐点亮
AThe lights are turningon
一道银光延亘至海
pA silver shine that stretches to the sea
此景专为两人定制
FThat s tailor made for two
可惜这两人是你我
FWhat a shame those two are you and me
若换作另一对男女
Some other girl and guy
会爱上这迷幻天空
Would love this swirling sky
但这里只有你和我
But there s only you and I
我们没可能在一起
PAnd we ve no shot got
绝对成不了
pThis could never be
你不是我钟意的类型
You re not the type for me Really
目光相对擦不出火花
FAnd there s not a spark in sight
可惜了这美妙的夜晚
What a Waste of a lovely night
你说什么感觉都没有
You say there s nothing here
这件事我说了算
pIthink IIl be the one to make that call
你会给我打电话
But call yoU II
穿着廉价涤纶西装
pAnd though you look so cute in your polyester suit
你说得对
You re right I d never fall foryou atall
也许这能迷住
PAnd maybe this appeals
或是幻想浪漫的姑娘
pOrto any girl who feels there s some chance for romance
但我心里真的毫无波澜
But I m frankly feeling nothing pIs that 50
很高兴你也有同感
Good to know so you agree
没错
AThat s right
可惜了这美妙的夜晚
NWhat a way to Waste of a lovely night